Brazilian developer with 10 years of experience as a designer, so I'm looking for a company where both skills come into play.

I am proficient within React (HTML, CSS, JS) and I have a solid knowledge of Rest API using Node.js, Express, MySql (Knex.js).

With a background as a designer, I am also highly skilled in quickly mock-up ideas and I also have vast experience designing art exhibitions and catalogs.

CONTACTS

+45 42 59 45 75 tiago86g@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/tiago86g

behance.com/tiago86g

github.com/tiago86g

SKILLS



MySql

Knex.js



REST API

Postman



Firebase

Styled components



Storybook.js UI/UX design





Typografy Branding

LANGUAGES

Portuguese

Native



Danish

Advanced





Tiago Gonçalves

EDUCATION

Hack Your Future - CPH Full-stack web development HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Databases, Node.is, Knex, React. 2019 - 2020

Superior School of Industrial Design / UERJ Bachelor of Graphic Design and Product Design Thesis: A typographic study for adult education 2006 - 2011

EXPERIENCE

Full stack developer HYF (anna.co)

Graphic designer **TUBA Denmark**

2019 to 2020

Therapy and counseling for young people who have grown up in families with alcohol or drug abuse

- Chat app for internal communication in restaurants

- New visual identity, marketing campaigns

Graphic designer Fairytell IVS

2020

International app for children's books

Anna makes restaurant hiring easier.

- Design and adaptation of books to different languages

Nordic film festival created by the Danish Cultural Institute - Visual identity (logo, invitation, flyer, folder, catalog, poster,

Graphic designer Ponte Nórdica

2016, 2018 and 2020

(Nordic Bridge)

Exhibition designer Camp

2019 to 2020

Exhibition space for art & debate about migration politics

- Designing and building the exhibition

banner and social media)

- Graphic material for the exhibition

Art Director Azougue Editorial

2011 to 2017

Brazilian publishing house focusing on artistic literature and cultural intervention

- E-commerce management - VTEX platform

- Development of a video streaming platform

- Graphic design
- Contact point for authors, stakeholders and suppliers

Graphic design **RNP**

2009-2011

A platafrm that connects people and institutions in an environment that enables knowledge production.

- Creating design for complex data charts
- Design of presentation material for sponsors